the HL7 community is filled with super smart
passionate people
who give a lot of their time and energy
through their day jobs as well as their personal time
to really help forge standards that can help us
fuel software
to help clinicians and care teams help patients
we're really staying on top of what's the cutting edge
people think about interoperability
just exchanging the data
but at the meeting this year
we actually talked about AI
the oddest thing people are talking about
if you're here
you're being challenged all the time by these people
so your products improve by just
exchange of ideas with all the
smart people in this community
the place to begin if you'd like to get involved with
hl7 is Zulabchat fire
org it's an open
online community where you can start asking questions
start meeting people
start learning what the community is all about
if you're the kind of person that wants to understand
if you're the kind of person
that has in depth knowledge that can be helpful
it's a place to actually make it happen
we really need
new people joining an actual seven working group
community it really would
help us to produce better standard
and we need to grow as a community
to make this world a better place